directoryisland.info 2007-10-11

# Privacy policy.

**

OUR PRIVACY POLICY

**

**[http://DirectoryIsland.info](http://directoryisland.info/) is absolutely committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors. **We collect basic information from online visitors who ask to be on our newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements. Anyone who wishes can choose to be removed from our mailing list at any time.

You will deal with our automated emailer, not a salesperson. We will NEVER hard sell. Unless you specifically ask for a live person to respond, all emails will be from a computer. I understand that many people wish to remain anonymous... and not be haggled with. I understand that you do NOT want a hype-spewing salesperson contacting you and talking down to you.

** We respect your privacy. **

**

We will _never_ sell, barter, rent, or give out your email address to anyone. We keep all information to ourselves. Like other Web sites, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

**

Our aim is to keep all information secure. _In fact, we give tips on how to improve security_. We offer reviews of the top SECURITY SOFTWARE: spyware, virus, trojan, firewall, etc. Also, we have a practical, easy to implement, attractive Verdana 12 font, NON-BORING security and self defense checklist manual that we publish. 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Your profile is protected by all possible measures. We are constantly searching for the top security measures (software firewalls, hardware firewalls, etc.).

**Disclaimer**

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on http://DirectoryIsland.info to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by http://DirectoryIsland.info and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by http://DirectoryIsland.info may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

**Newsletter subscription**

> > When you register for newsletters please consider entering a "nickname" in the name field. We suggest this because we put this name in the SUBJECT line when we send out emails. When you check your email and see this email (with your nickname in the subject field) you'll realize it isn't spam...and that you actually requested it. ** **
>> 
>> Internet Traffic Generator Ezine  
>>   
>> ---  
  
#### Virus software. [ McAfee Virus software](http://click.linksynergy.com/fs-bin/click?id=/z/*aSpTwls&offerid=50252.10000015&type=3&subid=0). 'Here's something every online person should have... [ Computer security software: Firewall](http://www.tkqlhce.com/4e66cy63y5LNRMTTRULNMOUQSMR). Now, if you are on a network/use a router...at least using my experience (as I have Zone Alarm's Firewall)...you may have to restart it every now and then. Oh, and the firewall is free to download. After 2 weeks you lose some features unless you upgrade.

**To unsubscribe, get removed, taken off our mailing list...**

**Simply reply to any email we send with "unsubscribe" typed in the subject. Or, click the contact link on our site and write "unsubscribe" in the form name or comment field.**

**CREDIT CARDS**

All credit card transactions occur over a secure connection. We do NOT store credit card numbers. We use a secure server.

**EXTERNAL LINKS**

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

© Copyright 1996-2004. All rights reserved.  
http://http://DirectoryIsland.info _ [http://DirectoryIsland.info](http://directoryisland.info/)_

_  Terms of Use and Disclaimer_
